Guide to the Francis G. Scheider papers, 1940-1988
Scheider, Francis G. papers, 1940-1988
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Francis G. Scheider papers, 1940-1988
4856
Francis G. Scheider, 1932-1989.
9.3 cubic ft.
Subject files, field records, reports, checklists, photographs, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files, field records, reports, and checklists, photographs, and other papers of an expert birder from the Rochester, New York area; records pertain mostly to Central New York State, but include accounts of trips to Alaska, Florida, and other places.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Francis G. Scheider was a birder, amateur ornithologist, and field collaborator of the Cornell University Laboratory of Ornithology.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, field records, reports, and checklists, photographs, and other papers of an expert birder from the Rochester, New York area; records pertain mostly to Central New York State, but include accounts of trips to Alaska, Florida, and other places.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Scheider, Francis G., 1932-1989.; Cornell University. Laboratory of Ornithology.
Subjects:
Birds--Societies, etc.; Bird watchers--New York (State); Ornithology.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Alphabetical subject files
Boxes 1-3, 10
Series II. Chronological records and reports
Boxes 3-12
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Alphabetical subject files
  Includes birding trips to Alaska and other states; New York State Breeding Bird Atlas Project; Kingbird; Christmas counts; New York State Avian Record Committee; correspondence with individuals.
  - Alaska Trip, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Alaska II Trip, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Alaska II - Wings Inc. Trip, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Birds - Buteo (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Attu, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Attu - Fall Trip, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Attu, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Attu, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Attu, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - "Birds of the World", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bird Papers and Reprints, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bird Programs, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Breeding Bird Atlas Project (New York State), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16-42)
  - Burtt, Ben, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Chincoteague, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Christmas Count Maps - Central New York (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
  - Christmas Counts, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cornell Ornithology Lab Newsletter, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Coronado National Forest - Cove Creek Canyon (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Delmarva, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Derby Hill - Hawk Data, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Derby Hill Spring Raptor Summary, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Florida Trip, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Florida - Dry Tortugas, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Florida, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Genesee Ornithological Field Report, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gordon, Dave, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Harper, Ed, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Haugh, John R., 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii Material, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, H. McClure, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9-12)
  - Kingbird Reports - Summer, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Kingbird - Fall, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kingbird - Fall, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15-17)
  - Kingbird - Winter, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kingbird - Spring, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kingbird - Summer, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Kingbird - Fall, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kingbird - Winter, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kingbird - Summer thru Spring, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Kingbird - Spring, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Kingbird - Summer, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kingbird - Winter, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kingbird - Spring, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Kingbird, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Kingbird - Spring and Summer, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Kingbird, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Leidwinger, Lou - letters from, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Life Lists (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Life List - North America, 1940-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Maine, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Massachussetts, Cape Ann Trips; Cumulative Totals, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Massachussetts, Cape Ann - Yearly Lists, 1974-1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Massachussetts, Cape Ann Birdwatch, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Massachussetts, Parker River, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Massachussetts, Rockport, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Massachussetts, Eateries and Hostelries, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Meade, Gordon M., 1964-1974 (Box 2, Folder 40-42)
  - Minor, William and Maureen - Red-tailed hawk, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - New York, Jamaica Bay Wildlife Refuge (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - New York State Avian Record Committee (NYSARC) - List for Regional Edition, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - NYSARC - Accepted, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 45-46)
  - NYSARC - Unresolved, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NYSARC, 1979-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NYSARC, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NYSARC, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYSARC, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYSARC, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - New York State Federation of Bird Clubs, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Oswego-Fulton Christmas Count Material, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Nov. Cumulative Totals, 1965-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Recher, Harry F., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - San Diego Trip, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - San Diego and Southern California, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Savoloja[?], Terry (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Skaneateles Christmas Count Material, 1972-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Gerald, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Robert J., 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Syracuse Christmas Count, 1967-1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Tug Hill Material, 1953-1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - VIREO, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Walcott, Charles, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wildlife Refuges (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Miscellany, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Miscellany, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Miscellany, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Miscellany (Box 3, Folder 28-31)
- Series II. Chronological records and reports
  Includes field records; regional reports; field checklists; birding notes; printed material.
  - Regional Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 32-36)
  - Individual Reports - May-Feb., 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Individual Reports - Dec.-Mar., 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Field Records, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Field Records - Apr., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Field Records - May, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Field Records - June-July, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Field Records - Aug.-Oct., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Field Records - Winter Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Field Records - June 1-Aug. 15, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Field Records - Aug. 15-Nov. 30, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Field Records, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Field Records, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Field Records - June-Aug. 15, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Field Records - Aug. 15-Nov., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Field Records, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Field Records - Jan. Waterfowl, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Field Records - Aug. 15-Nov., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Field Records - Dec. 1-Mar., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Field Records, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Field Records - Jan.-Aug. 15, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Field Records - Aug. 15-Nov., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Mar., 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Region V Report - Aug., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Field Records, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Field Records - Summer thru Spring, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kingbird - Summer, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kingbird - Winter, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Winter Summary, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Field Checklist, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Field Records, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-Aug., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fall Shorebird Migration in Central New York, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Field Checklist, Field Records, Region V Summary, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  - Regional Lists, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Field Records - Big Run, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Region V - Apr.-May, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Region V - June-Aug., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Region V - Aug.-Nov., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-Aug., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Mar., 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Field Checklist - June-Aug., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Field Records - Aug.-Nov., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Mar., 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Big Run - May, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Field Checklist - July-Sept., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Field Records - Aug.-Nov., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Mar., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Field Records, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  - Field Checklist - May, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Field Checklist - June-Sept., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Field Records - Aug.-Nov., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
  - Field Checklist - June-Aug., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Regional Reports - Summer, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Oct., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Regional Reports - Fall, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Field Checklist -Nov.-Dec., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Regional Reports - Winter, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26-27)
  - Field Checklist, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Regional Reports - Spring, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Field Records - May, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Field Checklist - Spring, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 30-32)
  - Regional Reports - Summer, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Field Records - Aug.-Dec., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Onondaga Audubon Society, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Field Checklist - June-Sept., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fall Regional Reports, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Regional Reports - Winter, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Winter - Waterfowl Census, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Regional Reports - Spring, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Regional Reports - Summer, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Regional Reports - Fall, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-Apr., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Field Checklist - May-Sept., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Regional Reports - Winter, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Big Run - May 19, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Regional Reports - Spring, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Field Checklist - June-Aug., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Regional Reports - Summer, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Regional Reports - Fall, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Regional Reports - Winter, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Mar., 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Field Checklist, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Regional Reports - Spring, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Field Records - Apr.-May, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Big Run - May 18, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Field Records - June 1-Aug. 15, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Field Records - Aug. 15-Nov. 30, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Region V, Oneida Lake Basin - Fall, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Region V - Waterfowl, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Field Records - Winter (includes Christmas Counts), 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Region V, Oneida lake Basin - Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-Oct., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Region V Material - Apr.-May, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Field Records - Sept.-Dec., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Field Checklist - Nov.-Dec., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Field Checklist - June-Sept., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Field Records - Region V - Sept.-Nov., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Feb., 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Field Records - Region V - Mar.-May, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Field Checklist - July-Dec., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Field Records - Nov.-Dec., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Feb., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Waterfowl Census - Jan., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Field Records - June-Aug., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Field Records - Sept.-Oct., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Region V - Big Run - Sept.-Nov., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Region V, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Field Checklist - July-Dec., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Region V - Oneida Lake Basin - Dec.-June, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Field Records - Dec.-Feb., 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Onondaga Audubon Society - Minutes, etc., 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Field Records - Region V - June-Aug., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Field Checklist - July-Dec., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Field Records - Sept.-Nov., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Field Records - Region V - Dec.-Feb., 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Onondaga Audubon Society, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Field Records, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Big Bend Trip Material, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Field Records - Spring (Mar.-May), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Field Records - Summer (June-Aug.), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Field Checklist - June-Aug., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Field Records, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Field Checklist - July-Sept., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Field Checklist - July- Sept., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Field Checklist - Oct.-Dec., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Field Checklist - June-July, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Field Checklist - Aug.-Dec., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kingbird - Winter, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kingbird - Spring, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
  - Field Records - Nesting Season, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Field Checklist - June-Aug., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Field Checklist - Sept.-Dec., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-July, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Field Checklist - Aug.-Dec., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Field Records - Fall, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Field Records - Winter, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
  - Field Records - Spring, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - Field Records - Summer, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
  - Field Checklist - July-Dec., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-June, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Field Checklist - July-Dec., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Field Checklist - Jan.-May, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Field Checklist - June-Dec., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Birding notes; printed material, including Birding, 1972 (Box 11-12)